你他妈要干什么
What the fuck do you want?
黑吃黑
第四季
第七集
想跟我说说你这些淤青是哪来的吗
You want to tell me how you got those bruises?
不太想
Not really.
你怕你说了  我们会不把孩子还给你
You afraid if you do, you won't get your kids back?
我在想
I'm starting to wonder
也许我应该更怕你们把孩子还给我
if I should be more afraid of getting them back.
我不配做他们的母亲
I don't deserve to be their mother.
也许我不配得到比现在更多的东西了
Maybe I don't deserve anything more than exactly what I got.
我给你开个后门
I'm gonna give you a free pass.
现在你说的话  不会影响我的监护权评语
Nothing you say now will affect my custody recommendation.
我保证不会记录下面的话
You have my word. This is off the record.
你为什么要这样做
Why would you do that?
因为不管你信不信  我想帮你
Because believe it or not, I'm trying to help you...
可不知道真相就没法帮
And I can't without the truth.
我又让她身处险境了
I put her in danger again.
谁  蒂法吗  她回家了
Who, Deva? She was home?
发生什么了
What happened?
他们来找我了
They came for me.
谁来找你了  卡莉
Who came for you, Carrie?
你想知道真相
You want the truth?
我是个骗子
I'm a liar.
我骗家人  骗丈夫
I lied to my family. I lied to my husband.
戈登  他从不说谎
Gordon, he never lied.
而我也仅仅不妄言他的事了
And his truth is the only one I have left.
他把他全部的生命
He dedicated his whole life
都奉献给了打击镇上的腐败
to fighting corruption in this town.
而你认为你必须把这件事进行到底
And you feel you have to see it through
因为他是为了救你而死
because he died saving you.
-没那么简单  -那帮帮我
- It's not so simple. - Then help me.
帮我弄清楚  帮我搞明白  卡莉
Help me out with it. Help me understand, Carrie.
真相是什么
What's the truth?
卡莉  帮我
Carrie, help me--
真相是我从没停止过爱别人
That I never stopped loving somebody else.
我知道  我需要停止抗争
I know, I have to stop this fighting.
不
No.
你起的头  要由你做完
You have to finish what you started.
你这算什么心理医生
What kind of shrink are you?
这不是作为一个心理医生的话
This is not the shrink talking.
是作为一个父亲的话
This is the father in me.
我知道在你解决这件事之前
And I know that until you make peace with this,
无法成为你的孩子们需要的那种家长
you can't be the parent that your children need.
那就解决它吧
So go finish it.
我的毒品呢
Where's my drugs?
他们把所有东西都拿走了
They took everything.
谁们
Who did?
我  我不
I-- I don't...
你让加尔文·邦克把我的毒品拿走了
You let Calvin Bunker take my drugs? Huh?
你让邦克把我的毒品拿走了
You let Bunker take my drugs?
我是维罗妮卡
Hey, it's Veronica.
今早你不见了
You disappeared on me this morning.
无论如何  我找到了我们强奸案的被害人
But anyway, I tracked down our statutory rape victim.
她说的话都没错
She said all the right things,
但我心里的测谎器响个不停
but my bullshit meter is ringing.
无论如何  我要回酒店了  回电
Anyway, I'm going back to the hotel, so call me
我给你说说...
and I can fill you in on the--
酒店监控显示道森
Okay, hotel surveillance shows Dawson
昨天快十二点离开大楼
leaving the property a little before noon yesterday.
我让所有在岗的副警长都出去找她了
I've got every available deputy out searching for her.
联调局动员了一个特遣部队
FBI is mobilizing a task force.
她活不了那么久
She won't live that long.
我们必须马上找到她
We have to find her now.
怎么找
How?
胡德  我已经追踪这个混蛋几个月了
Hood, I have been hunting for this son of a bitch for months
没有任何有用的线索
and all I got is dead ends.
那个姑娘呢
What about the girl?
自焚的那个
The one that burned herself.
盖尔·威斯克
Gail Westcott.
我们搜了她公寓三遍
We searched her apartment three times.
找不到任何与博德有关的线索
We can't find a single connection to Bode.
我已经递交了调查她手机记录的加急申请
I did request an expedited subpoena for her cell phone records,
但也需要几天时间
but that's still gonna take a few days.
手机在你这里吗
You still got the phone?
在  我是说  剩余的部分在
Well, yeah, I mean, what's left of it.
我们走吧
Let's go.
我见过这个表情
I've seen that look before.
我需要你帮忙
I need your help.
有些事是永远不变的  对吧
Some things never change, do they?
就像老日子
Just like old times.
老头最懂老日子
You're the expert on old.
等一下  我认识你
Wait a minute. I know you.
什么
Excuse me?
在金属工厂跟乌克兰黑帮枪战时
You and I were in a gunfight together
我们是一起的
with the Ukrainian gangsters at the metalworks.
纠正一下  是我在枪战
Correction, I was in a gunfight.
而你在地上躺着  哭着喊着说你的破腿
You were lying on the floor crying about your motherfucking leg.
包里是什么
What's in the bag?
手机  我要看通话记录
Cell phone. I need the call history.
过去几天的
Last few days.
恐怕没剩多少能用来...
Look, I'm afraid there's not much to work with there--
你们的技术警察可没戏
Maybe for your police techs.
跟那位鲍曼小妞有关系吗
This got something to do with the Bowman girl?
是的
Yeah.
给我十五分钟  糖果  我电脑呢
Give me 15 minutes. Sugar, where's my computer?
就在你之前放的地方
Exactly where you left it.
它自己又没长腿
Well, it ain't gonna fetch itself.
操
Fuck!
我进去了
I'm in.
高温弄乱了大部分内存
The heat scrambled most of the internal memory,
但还有足够的原始数据
but there was still enough raw data
让我来找到原始序列号黑进日志
for me to recover the ESN and hack the log.
虽然我听不懂你在说什么
I have no idea what you're saying,
但真他妈怀念听到你说这些
but I sure as hell missed hearing you say it.
那女孩自焚是发生在什么时间
What time did that girl set herself on fire?
上午七点
7 a.m.
她那天早上有打过电话吗
She make any calls that morning?
在她自焚前两小时里有五个通话记录
Five in the two hours before she grilled herself.
都是和同一个号码
All to the same number.
博德
Bode.
给我号码  我会让我的人追踪一下
Give me the number. I'll have my people do a trace.
我已经追踪到了  你快跟上吧  警察
I already traced it. You best keep up, cop.
号码的主人叫金姆·牛顿  认识她吗
Belongs to a Kim Newton. You know her?
不认识  但我猜她和博德有关
No, but I'm guessing she's connected to Bode.
这是地址
Address.
谢啦
Thanks.
谁他妈让你进来的
Who the fuck let you in here?
我要找加尔文
I'm looking for Calvin.
你是在找打
You must also be looking to get your ass kicked.
邦克先生拿了一些不属于他的东西
Mr. Bunker took something that didn't belong to him.
我老板想要回来
My employer would like it back.
这样啊  你可以告诉普罗科特
Yeah? Well, you can tell Proctor
让他去死
to go fuck himself.
他已经出局了
We're putting him out of business.
明白了
I see.
-别激动  -打他
- Easy! - You, you!
你是联调局特工
You're an FBI agent.
是的
Yeah.
你是连环杀手
And you're a serial killer.
我并不是因为喜欢
I don't kill them
而杀他们的
because I like to, you know.
我知道
I know.
你杀他们是因为你疯了
You kill them because you're insane.
都是有联系的  对吗
It's all relative, right?
并不是
Not really, no.
你以为撒旦跟你对话
You think Satan speaks to you.
根本就没有撒旦
There is no Satan.
所以  你是疯了
Ergo, you're insane.
你不怕我  不是吗
You're not afraid of me, are you?
不是针对你
Oh, don't take it personally.
我只是太多次知道幕布后的秘密了
I've just seen behind the curtain one too many times.
什么幕布
The curtain?
对啊  像《绿野仙踪》
Yeah, you know, like "The Wizard of Oz".
有强大魔力的法师
Turns out the big powerful wizard
结果只是烟雾和镜子
is just smoke and mirrors,
一个会点儿把戏的老神经
a delusional old fart with a few magic tricks.
你知道我怎么想的吗
You know what I think?
怎么想的
What's that?
我觉得你已经抓了足够多的巫师
I think you've taken down enough wizards to wonder
发现可能他们知道一些你不知道的事
if maybe they know something that you don't.
也许除了你告诉自己的话以外
That maybe there are truths
还有其它的真相
other than the ones you tell yourself.
那些真相
And those truths
让你遭受重创
have fucked you up so badly
你甚至都不知道什么时候去害怕了
that you don't even know when to be afraid.
我不害怕让你困扰
It bothers you I'm not afraid.
让你觉得虚弱
Makes you feel impotent,
没有那么强大了
less powerful.
你概括不出我
You can't profile me.
我不需要
I don't have to.
我已经抓住你了
I already caught you.
我喜欢你  维罗妮卡
I like you, Veronica.
但你还是会把我的心挖出来的
But you're still gonna cut my heart out.
是的
Yes, I am.
所以你懂我说的了吧
See what I mean?
他妈的神经病
Fucking insane.
怎么了
What's wrong?
我刚接到一个电话
I just got a call
一群加尔文的人在俱乐部被发现死亡
about a handful of Calvin's guys dead at the clubhouse.
-你觉得是加尔文干的  -不  都是他的人
- Do you think Calvin did it? - No, they're his guys.
我觉得兄弟会要开战了
But I think the Brotherhood is going to war.
在我对付加尔文的时候
And I don't want to have to worry about you
不想还要担心你的安危
while I'm dealing with Calvin.
你在布罗克的房子这儿不安全了
You're not safe here at Brock's house anymore.
我和戴德郡的朋友说过了
I spoke to a friend in Dade County.
他是位退休的警察
He's a retired cop.
他在坦伯利岛有个住处
He's got a place in Turnberry Isle.
你和汉克暂时在那里是安全的
You and Hank will be safe there for the time being.
-不会太久的  -你不明白
- It won't be for long. - You don't get it.
无论我们跑到那里  只要加尔文还活着
No matter where we run, as long as Calvin's breathing,
他就不会放过我的
he's not gonna let me go.
是我
Yeah, it's me.
我他妈又一次给你留言
I'm talking to your fucking voicemail again.
这是你最后的机会  玛吉
This is your last chance, Maggie.
告诉我你他妈的在哪儿
Tell me where the fuck you are
不然我发誓会毁了
or I swear to God I will destroy--
打给我
Call me back.
妈的
Oh, shit.
你真以为我会就这么过去吗
You really think I'll let this stand?
愚蠢的婊子  这事他妈的不会过去的
You stupid bitch. This will not fucking stand.
我他妈要宰了你
I will fucking end you.
我他妈要把你的肺扯掉
I will rip your fucking lungs out
然后活活憋死你
and I will strangle you with them.
加尔文
Calvin?
你好  马丁
Hello, Martin.
你到底在干什么
What the hell are you doing?
苍天啊
Jesus Christ.
他妈愚蠢的亚洲佬
Stupid gook motherfucker!
华盛顿特区
参议员米彻姆  感谢你肯来见我
Senator Mitchum, thank you for seeing me.
我想肯定是要紧事
I figure if it wasn't important,
不然你就直接给我打电话了
you would have just called me.
那么出什么事了
So what is it?
出现了些并发症
We had some complications.
我们不允许出现任何并发症
We can't afford any complications,
这些人不能有并发症
not with these people.
不然咱俩就休想有好日子过
Or we both wake up strangled by our own tongues.
我明白  所以我才来找你
I know that. That's why I'm here.
是生产环节出问题了吗
You're having production problems?
不  生产如期进行
No, production is on schedule.
是人员方面出问题了
I'm having personnel issues.
警察署
Sheriff's Department.
有人吗
Hello.
去周围看看
Check around back?
门开了
It's open.
有人要来吗
We having company?
稍后来
Later.
我还没换好衣服呢
I'm not really dressed for it.
如果你在倒酒  我也想喝点
I could use a drink if you're pouring.
你想喝什么
What would you like?
威士忌  谢谢
Whiskey, please.
你还真让我用吸管
You're really gonna make me
喝最后一杯酒啊
drink my last drink through a straw?
咱俩都知道给你松绑了  你就想逃跑
We both know if I untie you, you'll try to run.
然后我还得动粗
Then I'll have to rough you up again
才能把你绑回桌上
to get you back on the table.
那邻居们会怎么想
And what would the neighbors think?
什么都没有  我去楼上看看
Nothing. I'll check upstairs.
好
Okay.
维罗妮卡·道森
特别探员
那么谁会过来
So who's coming over?
就几个朋友
Just some friends.
你要举办仪式
You have a ritual.
没错
Yeah.
楼上什么都没有
Upstairs is clear.
她来过这
She was here.
该死
Oh, shit.
可现在人不在这
Well, she's not here now.
我在想这地方有没有地下室
I wonder if this place has a basement.
撒旦无意让你杀我  我碰巧出现了而已
Satan didn't tell you to kill me. I just showed up.
我不能放了你
I can't let you live.
或许我可以跟你和
Maybe I could just join you
你的兄弟们一起祭拜
and worship with you and your buddies.
不行
No.
为什么
Why not?
因为根本没有撒旦  记得吧
Because Satan doesn't exist, remember?
我很确定你说过这话
I'm pretty sure you said that.
想和个疯子达成一致
Nothing more annoying than a psychopath
真让人烦躁
who engages in Socratic debate.
现在怎么办
Now what?
你没事吧  怎么了
You okay? What's wrong?
你可真漂亮
You look beautiful.
抱歉  金姆  我对女的没兴趣
Sorry, Kim. I'm not into girls.
我叫莉莉斯
My name is Lilith.
不  不对
No, it's not.
我遇到德克兰时  你问过我
You asked me how the sex was
性爱的感觉如何
when I met Declan.
那感觉无与伦比
It was transcendent.
就像他侵占了我的灵魂
Like he was occupying my soul.
-那是强奸  -不
- It was rape. - No.
你当时还是个孩子
You were a child.
而他把我变成了女人
And he made me a woman.
-看  她的车  -什么
- Hey, her car. - What?
她的车在里面
Her car is in there.
搭把手
Give me a hand.
-这是她的车  -对
- This her car? - Yeah.
上面有血迹  该死
There's blood here. Shit.
胡德
Hey, Hood.
-怎么了  -得普利麻
- What? - Diprivan.
生产异丙醇的牌子
Brand name for Propofol.
迈克尔·杰克逊就死在这玩意上
Same shit that killed Michael Jackson.
-用来干什么的  -全身麻醉
- What's it used for? - General anesthesia.
这玩意儿为什么会出现在车库里
So what the fuck is it doing in a garage?
布罗克
Brock?
怎么了
Hey.
凶手  强奸犯
Killers, rapists,
毒贩子
drug dealers
四处横行  全是因为你
all walking the streets because of you.
不  是普罗科特  是普罗科特
No, it's Proctor. It's Proctor.
他逼我的  我发誓  他逼的...
He threatened me. I swear to God, he threat--
你他妈是地方检察官
You are the goddamn district attorney.
他拿我家人威胁
He threatened my family.
我有三个孩子  求你了
I have three kids. Please.
求你别这样
Please don't do this.
我要知道所有普罗科特参与的事
I want to know about everything Proctor has his hands in.
我只知道他想让我知道的
I only know what he wants me to know.
-你骗我  -没有
- Are you lying to me? - No.
不  等等
No, wait. Wait, wait, wait.
等等
Wait.
上周  上周他让我和手下们
Last week-- last week he made my office
封锁了旧地方机场的全部塔台记录
seize all the tower records from the old municipal airport.
为什么  谁来了
Why? Who's flying in?
埃米利奥·洛埃拉
Emilio Loera.
洛埃拉
Loera?
他是哥伦比亚贩毒集团的主要头目
He's a major player in the Colombian cartel.
普罗科特在给贩毒集团供货
Proctor's selling to the cartel?
我不知道  我发誓
I don't know. I swear to God, I don't know.
我要是知道一定会说的
I'd tell you if I did.
-回家吧  -什么
- Go home. - What?
辞职
You just quit.
带着孩子  离开女妖镇
Get your kids and get the hell out of Banshee.
胡德
Hey, Hood.
头晕是一阵一阵的
The dizziness comes in waves.
他们一定是给我们下药了
They must have drugged us.
你的手铐能打开吗
You got any give on your cuffs?
不行
No.
我也没戏
Yeah, me neither.
这是哪儿
What is this?
我也不知道  地下室吧
I don't know. Some sort of basement.
是啊
Of course.
你看清他了吗
Did you get a look at him?
他有天晚上找过我
He came to visit me the other night.
-谁  -博德
- Who did? - Bode.
你见过他了
You saw him?
那你他妈怎么什么都不说
Why the fuck didn't you say anything?
说不好  我可能是
I don't know. Maybe I was...
吓坏了
spooked.
他把我打晕了
He knocked me out.
等我醒过来时  他的刀就夹在我脖子上
And when I came to, he had a knife to my throat.
他当时完全可以杀了我
He could have killed me right there,
但他没有
but he didn't.
说什么要让我亲眼见证
Said he wanted me to bear witness.
-见证什么  -我也不知道
- To what? - I don't know.
但我感觉我们很快就能知道了
But I'm guessing we're about to find out.
道森也许也是在这里被抓起来了
So Dawson probably showed up and got the same treatment.
她可能还在这儿
She might still be here.
如果还没死的话
If she's not already dead.
虽然你努力的精神可嘉
Hey, I applaud your effort,
但你不可能挣脱不锈钢手铐的
but you're not gonna break out of stainless steel cuffs, okay?
不用打开手铐  弄断链子就行
You don't break the cuffs. You work the links.
走运的话  可能有缺口
If you're lucky, there's a defect.
你再试试你的
Why don't you try yours again?
好
All right.
我的右手松了些
My right hand is a little loose.
再使点劲就好
If I can just get a little more leverage.
太结实了  别折腾了
They're solid. Stop it.
胡德  停下
Hood. Hood. Stop!
看着我  别折腾了
Hey, hey, look at me. Give it up, all right?
我们出不去了
We're not getting out of here.
你知道最操蛋的是什么吗
You know what sucks about this?
除了我们将死之外
I mean, besides the fact that we're gonna die.
我从没当上我想成为的警长
I never got to be the sheriff I wanted to be.
我熬了很长时间
I waited so long for this.
熬到一个警长死了
I waited for one sheriff to die.
又得熬到你搞砸
And then I had to wait for you to burn out,
你也确实搞砸了
which you did in such a big way.
-请勿见怪  -不会
- No offense. - None taken.
我确实不是什么魅力男神
I mean, okay, so I'm not the most charming guy.
得罪过人
I rub some people the wrong way
也不会溜须拍马
and, you know, I can't kiss ass.
天性如此
It's just not in my nature, you know?
但我从不畏惧去对抗那些
But I've never been afraid to stand up to anybody
对镇上安康造成威胁的人
who threaten the well-being of my town.
我想成为那样的人  你明白吗
I wanted to be that guy, you know?
让人们感到安全的人
The guy that made people feel safe.
而我还没有做到
And I haven't done that.
我能问你件事吗
Can I ask you something?
-最后一次  -什么
- Be the last time. - What?
你他妈到底是谁
Who the fuck are you?
真的
Really.
你是谁
Who are you?
我知道你有很多秘密  胡德
Look, I know you got a lot of secrets, Hood.
连这都看不出来的话  我就太傻了
I'd be an idiot not to acknowledge that.
不  我才不要做什么有罪之人
No, we're not gonna do that condemned men
临终忏悔这种狗屁之事
confess their sins shit, all right?
我觉得  这正是
Yeah, I think that's
-我们要做的  -不  我们不这么做
- exactly what we're gonna-- - No, we're not.
那扇门随时都可能打开
Any minute now, that door is gonna open
我们会遭遇不测
and something very bad is gonna walk through it.
你难道不想问心无愧面对死亡吗
Now, don't you want to meet this with a clean conscience?
-不  闭嘴  -胡德  好好听着
- No, shut the fuck up. - Come on, Hood, please listen.
就回答我的问题吧
Then just answer the fucking question for me.
-别问了  布罗克  -我不会放弃的
- I said drop it, Brock! - No, I'm not gonna drop it!
我要知道
I want to know!
你为什么来这  为什么当警察
Why are you here? Why did you become a cop?
我不是警察
I am not a cop!
我他妈从来就不是警察
I never was a fucking cop!
你在说什么
What are you--?
-什  什么意思  -我不是卢卡斯·胡德
- What does that-- what does that mean? - I'm not Lucas Hood!
我看着他死的
I saw him die.
我捡起他的钱包  我变成了他
I picked up his wallet and I became him.
不可能  我不  你
That's not even possible. I don't-- what are you--
我是个谎言  布罗克  我是冒牌货
I'm a lie, Brock. I'm a fake.
我以前是小偷
I was a thief.
不只是小偷
Not just a thief,
我是渗透专家
I'm a fucking infiltration specialist.
钻石  黄金  艺术品  任何东西  我都能偷到
Diamonds, gold, art, anything, I could get it.
我能进入没人进得去的地方
The places no one could get into, I got in.
我本来顺风顺水
I had a good run,
但我被抓了  坐了15年牢
but I got caught and I did 15 years.
不  不  你在骗我
No, no. You're fucking with me.
得了吧
Come on.
你是前科犯  不可能
You're an ex-con? No.
-是的  -不可能
- That's right. - No.
还有谁知道
Who else knows about it?
西沃恩知道吗
Siobhan know?
最后知道了
In the end, yeah.
为什么你要这么做  为什么
Why would you do that? Why?
为什么要来这里假扮一个警察
Why would you come to this town and pretend to be a cop?
我不知道  我
I don't know. I...
我出狱的时候
When I got out...
一无所有
I had nothing.
不再是以前的我了
Whoever I was before was gone.
我谁都不是
I was no one.
我只知道我需要
All I knew is I needed to be close...
靠近那个唯一
to the one person who...
真正了解我的人
who really knew me.
卡莉·霍普韦尔
Carrie Hopewell?
安娜
Ana.
我只有她
She was all I had.
所以当我出狱时
So when I got out,
我查到了她的住址 然后来找她
I tracked her down and I came for her.
但她已经有了戈登  孩子和新生活
But she had Gordon and the kids and a life.
没错
That's right.
天啊
Oh, my God.
我成了
I became...
警长
sheriff.
但你不是  你从来不是
But you're not. You weren't.
可我每天都起床  穿上警服
Well, I was getting up every day, putting on the uniform.
最终我被谎言洗脑
Eventually the lie took over.
我相信了
I believed it.
我就是警长
I was the sheriff.
我是警察  我喜欢那工作
I was a cop and I liked it.
我特别喜欢
I fucking loved it.
不知怎么的
Somehow it just--
不知怎么的感觉很对
somehow it just felt right.
你所的所为跟对都沾不上边
There's nothing fucking right about what you did.
完全不对
It is the opposite of right.
你个混蛋
You son of a bitch.
我相信了你
I believed you.
我信任了你  听从了你
I trusted you. I followed you.
为你杀人
I killed for you.
不
No.
不  你是为你自己杀人
No, you killed for you.
不是我  我只是给你指明了路
Not me. I just showed you the way.
一个罪犯
A criminal.
真够荒唐的
That's rich.
我给一个罪犯当过副警长
I was deputy to a criminal.
天啊
Oh, God.
现在一切都说得通了
It all makes sense now.
全部
All of it.
我真蠢
I'm so stupid.
如果你不是卢卡斯·胡德
If you're not Lucas Hood...
那你叫什么
what's your name?
洛特斯警长
Sheriff Lotus.
很高兴又见到你
It's good to see you again.
还有你
And you.
奎克医生跟我说你们和道森探员是朋友
Dr. Quick tells me you're friends with Agent Dawson.
是的
That's right.
如果你伤害了她
And if you've hurt her in any way...
我他妈会灭了你
I'm gonna fucking kill you.
你们会喜欢今晚的
You fellas are in for a treat tonight.
是吗  你又要哄骗
Yeah? You gonna con another
一个可怜女生去自焚吗
poor girl into burning herself to a crisp?
盖尔是个忠实信徒
Gail was a true believer.
不  她是你为了你病态快感而蛊惑的
No, she was a confused and vulnerable young girl
一个茫然脆弱的年轻女孩
who you manipulated for your own sick pleasure.
看来你们要成为我今晚的宾客了
It looks like you're going to be my guests tonight.
问题是  我们有着装要求
Thing is, we have a dress code,
所以奎克医生要施展他的鬼斧神工
so Dr. Quick is going to work his magic
让你们看上去更像家人
and make you look a little more like family.
你闯进我的办公室
You bust into my office.
偷了我的摄像机
You steal my camera.
我不得不说
I gotta say,
我还盼着我们能再次相遇
I was hoping we would meet again.
大家过来吧  快开始了
Gather round, everybody. It's almost time to begin.
今晚我们有惊喜供品
We have an unexpected offering tonight.
我想他会开心的
I think he will be pleased.
光荣的撒旦
Gloria Satanas.
愿撒旦与你同在
Satanas vobiscum.
光荣撒旦
Gloria Satanas.
撒旦与你同在
Satanas vobiscum.
光荣撒旦
Gloria Satanas.
别担心  警长
Don't worry, Sheriff.
这一点都不痛
This won't hurt a bit.
也许痛一点
Well, maybe a little bit.
开始  光荣撒旦  恶魔与恶鬼
Here we go. Gloria Satanas et Belial et Spiritui maloso.
从开始
Sicut erat in principo,
到现在  与未来
et nunc, et semper,
世界永不灭
et in saecula saeculorum.
不  不
No, no.
离我远点
Stay the fuck away from me.
别过来  他妈的  离我远点
Stay away. Stay the fuck away from me!
阿门  恶凶于们我救但
Amen, evil from us deliver but
惑诱于陷许我不又
temptation into not us lead and
者债我负免亦我如
us against trespass who those forgive we as
债我免尔
trespasses our us forgive and
粮用日我  我与日今
bread daily our day this us give
尔望等我  焉天于如
heaven in is it as earth on
地于行承旨尔  格临国尔
done be will thy come kingdom thy
圣见名尔愿等我
name thy be hallowed
者父等我天在
heaven in art who Father our.
你没必要这样做
Hey, hey. You don't have to do this.
但我真的很想这样做
But I really want to.
你伤不了我  他不会允许的
You can't hurt me. He won't allow it.
是吗  那他不会介意我这样做
Oh, yeah? Then he won't mind if I do this.
有什么好笑的
What's so funny?
你真不清楚自己是多么微不足道
You have no idea how insignificant you really are.
彼此彼此  哥们
That makes two of us, pal.
德克兰
Declan!
胡德
Hood!
就是他杀了我侄女吗
Is that the man that killed my niece?
对
Yeah.
谢谢
Thank you.
解锁
锁闭
登录用户名或密码不正确
别麻烦了
Don't bother.
贾伯
Job.
你记得
You remembered.
我有钱  贾伯
I have money, Job.
很多钱
Lots of it.
你都想象不到
You have no idea.
两千三百六十二万
23.62 million.
还没算你在开曼群岛户头下
Not counting the 5.2 million in Swiss francs
偷偷存的五百二十万瑞士法郎
you have stashed away in the Caymans.
或者应该说  你曾拥有的
Or rather I should say you had.
你把我的钱怎么了
What did you do with my money?
甜心  那可不再是你的钱了
Oh, honey, that ain't your money no more.
你想要什么
What do you want?
我想要什么
What do I want?
我想要...
I want...
找回我生命中那该死的二十个月
20 months of my motherfucking life back.
那不是针对你
It wasn't personal.
你说得对
But you're right.
我害惨了你
I fucked you.
我们可以抛开过去
We can put the past behind us.
想一下我们联手可以做...
Imagine what you and I could do--
二十个月
20 months!
20 months
都在计划
of planning all the things
等我出去以后要做什么
I was going to do when I got out.
所有我要对那些
All the things I was going to do...
把我关进去的混蛋要做的事
to the motherfucker who put me there.
但我领悟以后
But I have since seen the light.
意识到  把你的小命杀掉
Erasing your worthless ass
也弥补不了我失去的时间
ain't gonna give me back the time you took.
你不准备杀我
You're not going to kill me?
不杀
No.
我要杀了自己
I'm going to kill me.
你想跟最棒的人较量
You wanted to fuck with the best.
现在你就是最棒的
Well, now you are the best.
现在你就是贾伯
Now you are Job.
从现在开始  任何人在任何时间想找我
From now on, anytime anybody comes looking for me,
都会来找你
they're gonna find you.
我破解过的每个安全系统
Every security system I ever cracked,
我坑过的所有组织
every organization I ever compromised,
我偷过的每一元钱
every dollar I ever stole,
到处都是你的痕迹
they all got your fingerprints on them now.
摩萨德  人民共和国
Mossad, People's Republic,
美国政府  以及各路不好惹的恐怖分子们
Uncle Sam, and a who's who of unsavory terrorist types,
都有笔账想跟你算算
they all got serious beef with you now.
婊子  我让你红了
Bitch, I just made your punk ass famous.
而且我有预感
And something tells me...
找你可比找我容易多了
you gonna be a hell of a lot easier to find than I ever was.
祝你短命愉快  傻逼
Have a nice short life, motherfucker.
贾伯  等等
Job, wait.
你不能对我这样
You can't do this to me.
贾伯
Job!